His past was taken. His vengeance is fueled.
The Stranger is a action, thriller, mystery film directed by Rob Lieberman.
The Stranger is a man with no name, no memory and
absolutely nothing left to lose.
But when he finds himself hunted by both the FBI and the
Russian mob, this amnesiac decides to fight back.
Pursuit cannot stop him.
Torture will not break him.
And with every beating, bullet and betrayal, he’ll remember another piece of the
horror that took away his career, his family and his identity.
The Stranger, played by Steve Austin.
Grace Bishop, played by Erica Cerra.
Stranger's Daughter, played by Calista Bashuk.
Stranger's Wife, played by Karly Warkentin.
Grandaughter Katya, played by Dalila Bela.
Mason Reese, played by Adam Beach.
The Stranger is a 2010 Canadian-American action film written by Quinn Scott, directed
by Robert Lieberman, and starring former WWE wrestler Steve Austin.
The film was released on direct-to-DVD and Blu-ray in
the United States on June 1, 2010.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.